Nathan S Jang

Software Engineer

Permanent Resident of the U.S.

Walnut Creek, CA (415) 317-5944 nathan.s.jang@gmail.com https://nathansjang.github.io/Portfolio/ linkedin.com/in/nathan-sb-j github.com/NathanSJang

SUMMARY

Software Engineer with a background in the Michelin starred culinary scene for 8 years. I am a self-starter who is a reliable and responsible individual, having experience in high pressure and fast paced working environments, successfully producing finest quality end results. I have a strong passion for learning, maintaining, and improving complex systems.

SKILLS

HTML | CSS & SASS | JavaScript | Python | React | Redux | GraphQL | Apollo-server | PostgreSQL | Express | MongoDB Mongoose | Material design | Bootstrap | Figma | Trello

PROJECTS

Chat_Chat (github) — React, Apollo-Server, GraphQL, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, Bootstrap, AWS

Make simple live chat app using React, Apollo-Server, GraphQL, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, and Bootstrap

KUSAKABE (github) — React, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose

Make an online order MERN stack app for famous Omakase restaurant named 'KUSAKABE' using React, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, and Material UI

Memories (github) — React, Redux, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose

React codealong, built SNS style MERN stack app for people's memories using React and Redux

EXPERIENCE

PinDrop Network, Remote — Software Engineering Intern

Jun 2021 - Present

Frontend engineering intern working on Landing page and UI components.

Ivyscope, Remote — Software Engineering Intern

APR 2021 - MAY 2021

Part-time fullstack engineering intern working on subscription emails, newsletters, and website build.

Kusakabe (One Michelin starred), The Shota, San Francisco, CA — Sushi & Kitchen Chef

OCT 2016 - MAR 2020

Trained and supervised new staff members as well as managing and leading the team. Ensure highest quality and timely delivery of course of the meal. Served as a sushi & kitchen chef in an Omakase (Chef's Prix Fixe Menu) restaurant.

EDUCATION

General Assembly, Software Engineering Immersive, San Francisco, CA

12 weeks of full-time coding bootcamp in Software Engineering program running from October 2020 to February 2021. Recognized and voted as "The most elegant coder".

California Culinary Academy, Culinary Arts, San Francisco, CA